paksoldiers.com 2012-12-15

# Privacy Policy - PakSoldiers | PakSoldiers

**Personally Provided Information  
**

You do not have to give your personal information to visit Paksoldiers.com. If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, comment, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

**» Website Traffic Analysis Software  
**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

**» E-mail Newsletters**

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our Daily Newsletter is powered by FeedBurner. We/Feedburner use information submitted by you in the same manner as we use contact information described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

**Third Party Advertising Partners**

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on PakSoldiers.Com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to  PakSoldiers.Com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –

http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**» External Links**

Our web sites contain links to other sites. PakSoldiers.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information.

Last updated: October 12, 2012
